Guide to the United Workers Union-Independent Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
United Workers Union-Independent records
1973-1980
1974-1978
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5690
5690-001
United Workers Union-Independent
8.25 cubic feet 11 boxes
Records of the United Workers Union-Independent and its precursor organization, the Staff Rights Organizing Committee of the University of Washington
Records of the Staff Rights Organizing Committee (SROC) and United Workers Union-Independent (UWU-I). SROC mobilized University of Washington staff to fight a discriminatory job reclassification that resulted in the first strike at the University of Washington in 1973. After the strike, members of the organizing committee formed their own union, United Workers Union-Independent. The union raised issues about the effects of racism and sexism on salaries that later became the concept of the Comparable Worth campaign. UWU-I's advocacy for the lowest-paid, unorganized women and people of color on campus prodded other campus unions to better represent these workers.
Records of the United Workers Union-Independent and its precursor organization, the Staff Rights Organizing Committee of the University of Washington. Includes photos, buttons, newsletters, leaflets, and press releases.
Records stored offsite; advanced arrangements are necessary. Please contact us for more information.
Open to all users.
Donor: Helen Gilbert, March 14, 2012
The visual materials that form part of this collection are described and indexed in
A Guide to the
.
United Workers Union-Independent$vArchives; University of Washington$xEmployees; Staff Rights Organizing Committee (University of Washington); Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington)
Discrimination in employment$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Equal pay for equal work$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Pay equity$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Sex discrimination in employment$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Strikes and lockouts$zWashington (State)$zSeattle
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor;; Labor History; Labor Unions; Women; Washington (State); Seattle
Newsletters; Photographs; Press releases; Buttons (information artifacts); Leaflets
- Publication: United Workers Organizer Volume 1, Number 1, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Canvas Banner, Circa 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Action Childcare Coalition, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Addresses and Telephone Numbers, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Affirmative Action: Seattle Public Schools, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Affirmative Action: University of Washington, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Affirmative Action, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Affirmative Action Office at University of Washington, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Affirmative Action Position Paper, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees: Washington Federation of State Employees: Legislative Reports, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees: Washington Federation of State Employees, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees: Washington Federation of State Employees, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Series includes notes of affection to and from wife, dog, and others.
- Native American Material, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Anniversary Celebrations, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Attendance, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Emma Boston, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Budget: University of Washington, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Buffalo Workers' Movement, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Bylaws and Changes, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Childcare, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- City Charter of Seattle: Criticism of Proposed Charter, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Citizens Review Board: Committee on Crimes Against Women, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW) Constitutional Convention, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Collective Bargaining Data: State Employees, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Comparable Worth, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Conference for Union and Working Women, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Correspondence with Management, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Daily Articles: Letters to the Editor, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Distribution: University of Washington, circa 1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Educationals, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Elections, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Faculty Senate, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Feminist Coordinating Council, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Feminist Coordinating Council Minutes, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Feminist Coordinating Council, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Feminist Coordinating Council, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Feminist Coordinating Council (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Feminist Coordinating Council (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Feminist Coordinating Council (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Financial Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Finances: Annual Audit Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Firefighters--Women, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Hospital Dietary Department (University): Working Conditions Investigation, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Food Service Worker Petitions, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Dietary Grievance, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Inez Garcia, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Graduate Opportunity Program for Women and Minority Students, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- The Union Grapevine: Washington Federation of State Employees Local 1488, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Grievance Policy and Guidelines, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Ron Chew Grievance, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Custodial Grievance, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- John McDonald Grievance, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Rosa Morales Grievance: Higher Education Personnel Board Hearing, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Mary Reeves and Clare Bright Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Telephone Switchboard Grievance, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Social Event Invitations, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- United Workers Organizer: Volume I, No. 5 & 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- History of United Workers Union- Independent, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Early History of United Workers Union-Independent, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Draft Principles and Bylaws, circa 1973 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Preamble and Bylaws, circa 1974 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Posters for Direct Actions, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. III, No. 5: "UW Administrators Frame Chicana", 1977 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. III, No. 4: "WPEA Strike Shakes up the State", 1977 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. III, No. 3 "New Governor- No Friend to Workers", 1977 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. III, No. 2 "Join the Fight for a Living Wage", 1977 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. III, No. 1, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. II, No. 7, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- United Workers Bulletin: Vol. II, No. 4, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. I, No. 6: Petition for raise, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- United Workers Organizer and Bulletin: Vol. I, No. 1 & 2, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. I, No. 1, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- United Workers Newsletter: Vol. I, No. 1, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- United Workers Bulletin: Vol. I, No. 2, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- United Workers Bulletin: Vol. I, No. 3, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. I, No. 2- October, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. I, No. 2- November, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. II, No. 6 & 8, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- United Workers Organizer: Vol. II, No. 5; Vol. IV, No. 2; Vol. V, No. 1, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Poster: Tell UW Regents No Layoffs, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Poster: Layoffs-Speed-ups- Sweatshops Where Does it Stop?, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Information Packet, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Publication: Workforce, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- What's Happenin': Bulletin to Members, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pamphlet Originals, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- The Ballard Voice, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Yvonne Wanrow, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- The Washington State Employee, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Washington State Nurses Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Washington State Conference for Women, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Seattle Women's Commission Nomination for Yolanda Alaniz, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Women Today: Vol. V, No. 22, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Women's Studies Program, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Woman's Week Calendar, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Pamphlet: Necessities for an Effective Affirmative Action Program, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Poster: Bosses Speed Up U.W. Workers, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chicano Soul Disco: Benefit for Rosa Morales, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Poster: Come to Our Social, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Worker Bill of Rights and Contract Proposal, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Meeting Summaries, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Poster: Come to Rosa Morales' Grievance Hearing, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Poster: Defend Free Speech, Come to Rosa Morales' Grievance Hearing, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Poster: Demand a Living Wage; Urging State Workers to Call Legislature, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Poster: Emercgency! UW Staff Meeting on Raises, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Poster: Fight for Your Budget, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Poster: Food Workers Demand Respect and Get It, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Poster: Layoffs, Speed-ups, Sweatshops Where Does it Stop, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Poster: Low Paid Workers Need a Raise, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Petition for Salary Raise to the State Legislature, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Petition to the Legislature on State Employee Salaries, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- The Washington State Coalition for Protective Legislation by Mary Reeves and Lois Harris, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Pamphlet: Radical Politics Make the Difference, by Yolanda Alaniz and Monica Hill, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Pamphlet: Raise the Roof for Our 1977 Wage Raises! (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Pamphlet: Raises? What Raises!, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Poster: Second Anniversary Celebration, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Poster: Sign the Petition for a $200 Raise, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Pamphlet: Sign the Petition for $200/mo. Across the Board, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Educational: Strike- Workers Strongest Weapon by Mary Reeves, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Poster: Tell U.W. Regents No Layoffs, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Poster: $200/mo. Raise Before the Legislators: House Bill #761, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- United Workers Organizes by Yolanda Alaniz, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- A Union that Wins by Yolanda Alaniz and Monica Hill, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Poster: United Workers Benefit, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Poster: Calls for $200/mo. For All State Workers, Not Just For A Few, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Poster: Stopped Management: Won John McDonald Grievance, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Flier: Outreach, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Flier: Rosa Morales Picket, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Letter: Rosa Morales Fired, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Flier: Fund raising Benefit, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Poster: Food Service Worker Raises: Starve or Freeze?, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Poster: Workers' Right to Childcare, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Poster: WFSE Bureaucrats Sell Out State Workers, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Reprint: Daily: Affirmative Action: Campus Fights Back, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Reprints: Chicana Movement, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Reprint: Daily: Chicano Protest, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Reprint: Daily: Sexual Politics, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Reprint: Daily: Sit-In Succeeds: United Workers' Demands Met, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Reprints: Seattle Times and Seattle P.I.: Strike, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Reprint: Daily: Strike History Has Lessons For Us, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Reprint: Daily: Strike Vote is only the beginning of change, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Reprint: Daily: UW food service workers demand emergency raise, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Reprint: Daily: United Workers demand across-the-board pay raise, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Reprints: Seattle P.I.: UW Budget OKd in Stormy Session; UW Union demands no layoffs, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Food Service Workers, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Bargaining Units at Higher Education Institutions, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- New Job Classifications with Proposed Salary Ranges, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- SROC Committees, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- SROC Dailys, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Draft: Letter to Cartwright, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- SROC Leaflets, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- SROC Strike Bulletins and Petition, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- SROC Press Releases, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- SROC Grievances and Forms, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- SROC Correspondence, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- SROC Injunction, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- SROC Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- SROC: Legislature, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- SROC Press Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- SROC Press Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Statewide: Letter to Absentees, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Statewide Organizing, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Report from the Strike and Defense Committee on Laws, Collective, and Legal Action, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- SROC 'The Organizer' Vol. I, No. 1-8, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- SROC Strike Bulletins No. 1- 5, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- University of Washington Bulletins on Reclassification, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- SROC's Testimony, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Miscellaneous Personal Notes, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- Statement by the Staff Rights Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Correspondence: To All Members of CSA and WFSE, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Report from Research Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- To the Organizer, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 90)
- Handout: Don't Be Fooled, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Handout: Protect Your Job- Attend the HEPB Meeting, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Handout: Round Two, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Handout: The Effects of Reclassification, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 94)
- Handout: We're Being Hit Hard, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 95)
- Handout: Hospital Workers: Why Strike?, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 96)
- Handout: Some Fact About the Position of Classified Staff and What SROC is Doing About it, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 97)
- Poster: SROC Strike Meeting, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 98)
- Handout: Strike Rally, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 99)
- Pamphlet: Strike Starts December 18, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 100)
- Poster: UW Staff Strike- December 18, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 101)
- Leaflet: Staff, Faculty, Students, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 102)
- Handout: Strike: Students Support S.R.O.C., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 103)
- Letter: Strike Support Request from other Unions, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 104)
- Announcement: Build the Strike at the University of Washington Community Rally, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 105)
- Poster: Strike to End Discrimination, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- Leaflet: Strike Continues...Unionizing Underway, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 107)
- Leaflet: Help Build the UW Strike, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 108)
- Letter to all Union Members, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 109)
- Letter to Faculty, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 110)
- Letter to Faculty: Request for Help, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Pamphlet: Strike Social, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 112)
- Strike Bulletin: Strike Begins Tomorrow, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 113)
- Membership: Phone Numbers and Addresses, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 114)
- Switchboard Grievance: Press, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 115)
- Newspaper Clippings (1 of 2), 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 116)
- Newspaper Clippings (2 of 2), 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Hospital Dietary, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 118)
- Press Statement: Chicano Protest at the University of Washington, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 119)
- Press Release Originals, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 120)
- Department of Romance Languages and Literature: Resolution in Support of Strike, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 121)
- Food Service Worker Leaflets, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 122)
- United Workers Organizer; Vol. IV, No. 1 & 2; Vol. V No. 1, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 123)
- Strike Kitchen Manual, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 124)
- Petition Against Reclassification, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 125)
- Publication: Contempt: Vol. 2, No. 3, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 126)
- Publication: Northwest Gay Review: Vol. 1, No. 1, 3, 4, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 127)
- Publication: The City Collegian: Vol. 9, No. 10, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 128)
- Publication: Pandora: Vol. IV, No. 7, 8, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 129)
- Publication: Outlook: "Strike, no- show decision Tuesday", 1973 (Box 4, Folder 130)
- Publication: The People's Health: Vol. 4, No. 1-2, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 131)
- Article: Seattle P.I. 'Moderates' Withdraw Support of UW Classified Staff Strike, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 132)
- Article: Seattle P.I.: UW Regents Delay Action, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 133)
- Article: Seattle P.I.: UW Workers Say They'll Strike Today, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 134)
- News Clippings, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 135)
- Publication: Seattle Sun, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 136)
- Campus Report: Publication for Faculty and Staff: Vol. 3, No. 4, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Daily Articles on Reclassification, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Daily Articles, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Daily Articles: Reclassfiction and Salary Discrimination, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Daily: Open Letter from President Cartwright to Monica Hill, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Daily Articles, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Daily Articles: Dissenter's letter and Faculty Tenureship Issues, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Daily Articles: Mike Neal Response to Monica Hill, Regents Report on Affirmative Action, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Daily Letter to the Editor: General Injustice of Raise System, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Daily Article: Feminist Focus: Wanda Adams, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Daily: Open letter from Jossie Anthonie, Joanne Ward and Teri Bach, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Daily Articles, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Publication: University of Washington Report: University Faces New Era, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Reprint Drafts: Daily and Times on Demand for $200/month Across the Board Raise, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous News Articles (1 of 3), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous News Articles (2 of 3), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous News Articles (3 of 3), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Layoffs, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Publication: AFSCME Public Employee, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- News Articles (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- News Articles (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Staff Rights Organizing Committee Arm Band, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Staff Rights Organizing Committee: Leaflets, Press, Agendas, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Leaflets From Other Radical Organizations, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Labor Law, 1962-1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Legislature, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Publication: The Lettuce Boycott, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Pierce County Library Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Publication: Maintenance Handbook: Part 2: Managing With-or Without-a Union, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Meeting Notices, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- National Organization for Women- Seattle Chapter, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Publication: Northwest Access: The Third World Monthly Journal, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Office of Equal Opportunity for Women: New Director, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Office Lease, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Open Housing Ordinance, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Other Organizations, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Free Leonard Peltier, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Publication: The People's Health: Vol. 3, No. 6, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Photographs, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- A List of Local, State and National Women's Political Organizations, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Publication of Southern Poverty Law Center: Poverty Law Report: Vol. 5, No. 2, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Press List, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Press Coverage: Reproductions, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- President's Overview: Monica Hill, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Press Releases, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Press Releases: United Workers Union-Independent, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Pamphlet: Necessities for an Effective Affirmative Action Program on the University of Washington Campus, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Packet Table of Contents, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Coalition on Protective Legislation (1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Coalition on Protective Legislation (2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Publication: Public Employee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Radical Women Conference Announcement, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Raise Campaign, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Research, 1965-1975 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Retirement: Initiative Measure No. 333, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Salaries, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Salary Analysis, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Salary Campaigns, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Blank Petitions: Salary Raise, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Salary Proposal, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Publication: The Scanner and King County Labor News, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Scholarships, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Seattle City Light Charter, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Seattle City Light Electrical Trades, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Seize the Time for Oppressed People (S.T.O.P.), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Service Employee International Union (SEIU) Strike, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Skits for Socials and Anniversary Celebration, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Leaflet: Social, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Sing-Alongs, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Speeches: Monica Hill, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Publication: the Spokeswoman: A crossroads of communication for women, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Staff Association "organizer": Vol. 2, No. 7, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- State Women's Council, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers: Strike Instructions, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Strike Support Resolution, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Supporters and Membership, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Survival Information: Notice to All Non Assistance Food Stamp Applicants, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- University of Washington Task Force on Personnel Rules and Procedures, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Title IX, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Title XX: Fact Sheet and Statement, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Tuition Increase: Statement by Monica Hill, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Other Unions, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Union W.A.G.E.: Women's Alliance to Gain Equality: West Coast Conference for Working Women, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Publication: Union W.A.G.E.: Women's Alliance to Gain Equality, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- The Daily: May, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Daily: June, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Daily: October, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- The Daily: November, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- The Daily: December, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- The Daily: January, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- The Daily: February, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- The Daily: March, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- The Daily: April (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- The Daily: April (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Drawer 4 Mixed Type (Box 8)
- History, Leaflets, Press Statements and News Articles, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Informational Packets, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Unfair Labor Practice, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Telephone Switchboard Services Group Grievance, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)